Bust a Moo
Home on the Range is a animation, family film directed by John Sanford.
When a greedy outlaw schemes to take possession of the "Patch Of Heaven" dairy farm, three determined cows,
a karate-kicking stallion and a colorful corral of critters join forces to save their home.
The stakes are sky-high as this unlikely animal alliance risk their
hides and match wits with a mysterious band of bad guys.
Maggie (voice), played by Roseanne Barr.
Mrs. Caloway (voice), played by Judi Dench.
Grace (voice), played by Jennifer Tilly.
Wesley (voice), played by Steve Buscemi.
Rusty (voice), played by G.W. Bailey.
Buck (voice), played by Cuba Gooding Jr..
Home on the Range is a 2004 American animated Western comedy
film produced by Walt Disney Feature Animation.
Written and directed by Will Finn and John Sanford, it stars the voices of Roseanne Barr,
Judi Dench, Jennifer Tilly, Cuba Gooding Jr., Randy Quaid, and Steve Buscemi.
It features original songs written by Alan Menken and Glenn Slater, and an
original musical orchestral score also composed by Menken.
Home on the Range is set in the Old West, and centers on a mismatched trio
of dairy cows—brash, adventurous Maggie; prim, proper Mrs.
Calloway; and ditzy, happy-go-lucky Grace.
The three cows must capture an infamous rustler named Alameda Slim for his
bounty in order to save their idyllic farm from foreclosure.
Aiding them in their quest is Lucky Jack, a feisty, peg-legged rabbit, and a selfish horse named Buck,
eagerly working in the service of Rico, a famous bounty hunter, who seeks the glory for himself.
Home on the Range premiered at the El Capitan Theatre in Los Angeles on March
21, 2004, and was released in the United States on April 2.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and was a box office failure, grossing
$145.3 million worldwide against a production budget of $110 million.
The film explores themes of farm, villain, outlaw, animals, psychotic.